{
    "id": "29d2749b5d75485a8918819ddec625b0",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The driver felt sluggish …………………………….. he had lost a lot of blood.",
            "description": "Because gives the reason for something.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… you are busy, I will wait in the lobby.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "As",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… he is too short, he cannot be a police officer.",
            "description": "As gives the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "So",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is neither a dog …………………………… a fox.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nor",
                "either",
                "or"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t walk ……………………………. I have broken my leg.",
            "description": "Because gives the reason for something.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "due to",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You are going to wear that dress ……………………………. you don’t like it.",
            "description": "Even if refers to present or future. ",
            "answers": [
                "even if",
                "even though",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………………… it was a balmy Sunday, I didn’t go out.",
            "description": "As shows the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Because of",
                "Due to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will not forgive her, ………………………………… she apologizes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "even if",
                "even though",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ran so fast ……………………………. I could not catch up with him.",
            "description": "Note the pattern so...that...\r\nSo shows the cause and that indicates the effect.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "hence",
                "therefore"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The higher you climb, ………………………….. it gets.",
            "description": "The comparative is used in both clauses in this structure. ",
            "answers": [
                "colder",
                "the colder",
                "the cold"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. he was the most eligible candidate, he didn’t get the job.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "Since"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the girl …………………………….. we are talking about.",
            "description": "Who is possible here in an informal style. ",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "which",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}